Irving R. Kaufman Papers
Manuscript Division, Library of Congress
- United States Court of Appeals, Second Circuit, 1942-1992 (Box 30-115)
  - Office Files, 1942-1992 (Box 34-115)
    - Federal Judicial Center
      - Seminars, 1966-1983, undated, (2 folders)
      - Subcommittee to Define and Describe Positions of Court Personnel, 1968
      - Training programs
        - Advocates, 1963-1968
        - Clerks, 1968-1970, undated
        - Probation officers, 1968-1969 (Box 73)
        - Referees, 1968-1969
      - Workshops, 1975-1989, (2 folders)
    - Federal rules
      - Appellate procedure, 1977-1982, undated
      - Criminal procedure, 1982
    - Foley Square Courthouse, New York, N.Y.
      - Building Operations Committee, 1974-1989
      - Maintenance, 1973-1988, undated
    - Institute for court management, 1969-1971, (3 folders)
    - Institute of Judicial Administration (Box 74)
      - Board of fellows, 1984-1989, undated
      - Breakfast meetings, 1985-1990, (2 folders)
      - Correspondence, 1983-1991, (4 folders)
      - Fund-raising meeting, 1990-1991
      - Miscellany, 1971-1991, undated
      - Report, 1984-1990, undated
      - Task force on asbestos litigation, 1991, (2 folders)
    - Joint Sentencing Institute, Denver, Colo., 1966
    - Judges (Box 75)
      - Ainsworth, Robert A., 1962-1982, (2 folders)
      - Anderson, Robert P., 1973-1978, undated
      - "A" miscellaneous, 1974-1987
      - Bazelon, David L., 1968-1978
      - Becker, William H., 1967-1971
      - Bell, Griffin B., 1967-1986
      - Biggs, John, 1961-1980
      - Blackmun, Harry A., 1970-1985
      - Bonsal, Dudley B., 1976-1984
      - Botein, Bernard, 1969-1974
      - Bratton, Howard C., 1967-1975
      - Breyer, Stephen G., 1986-1988
      - Brieant, Charles L., 1974-1988
      - Bright, Myron H., 1980-1988
      - Brown, John R., 1963-1964, undated
      - Browning, James R., 1976-1987
      - Bruchhausen, Walter, 1976
      - Bryan, Frederick v P., 1970-1978
      - Burger, Warren E., 1969-1991, undated, (6 folders) (Box 76)
      - Burke, Harold P., 1976-1981
      - "B" miscellaneous, 1978-1979
      - Cabranes, José A., 1981-1988
      - Campbell, William J., 1975-1985
      - Cannella, John M., 1977-1991
      - Cardamone, Richard J., 1981-1986, undated (Box 77)
      - Carter, James M., 1964-1980
      - Chambers, Richard E., 1967-1971
      - Clark, Charles, 1964, 1986-1990
      - Clark, Tom C., 1962-1987, (3 folders)
      - Craven, J. Braxton, 1967-1971
      - "C" miscellaneous, 1968-1991, undated
      - Devitt, Edward J., 1968-1991
      - Dimock, Edward J., 1969-1986
      - Dooling, John Francis, 1974-1981
      - Douglas, William O., 1973-1980
      - "D" miscellaneous, 1975-1989
      - Edwards, George C., 1968-1986
      - Estes, Joe Ewing, 1978-1990
      - "E" miscellaneous, 1975-1985
      - Feinberg, Wilfred, 1977-1988, undated (Box 78)
      - Foley, James T., 1966-1990, undated
      - Frankel, Marvin E., 1969-1983
      - Friendly, Henry J., 1983-1986, undated
      - "F" miscellaneous
      - Gash, Oliver, 1970-1972
      - Gewin, Walter P., 1968-1980
      - Gignoux, Edward T., 1970-1985
      - Ginsburg, Ruth Bader, 1979-1991
      - Gourley, Wallace S., 1968-1969
      - Gurfein, Murray J., 1970-1983
      - "G" miscellaneous, 1967-1990, undated
      - Heaney, Gerald W., 1969-1972
      - Higginbotham, A. Leon, 1969-1978
      - Hill, Irving, 1965-1979
      - Hufstedler, Shirley M., 1976-1979
      - "H" miscellaneous, 1961-1988, undated
      - Jameson, William James, 1967-1974 (Box 79)
      - Judd, Orrin G., 1970-1976
      - "J" miscellaneous, 1967-1986
      - Kelleher, Robert J., 1974-1991
      - King, James Lawrence, 1971-1985
      - "K" miscellaneous, 1979-1989
      - Levet, Richard H., 1971-1980
      - "L" miscellaneous, 1978-1981
      - MacMahon, Lloyd F., 1963, 1970-1989
      - Markey, Howard, 1978-1979, 1990
      - McCree, Wade H., 1968, 1978-1987
      - McGivern, Owen, 1974-1975, undated
      - McGowan, Carl, 1965, 1987
      - Medina, Harold R. 1990-1991, undated
      - Meskill, Thomas J., 1974-1980
      - "M" miscellaneous, 1967-1987, undated
      - Powell, Lewis F., Jr., 1970-1989, undated
      - Starr, Kenneth W., 1983-1989
      - Steckler, William E., 1966-1971
      - "S" miscellaneous, 1965, 1986-1987
      - Warren, Earl, 1962-1968
      - Werker, Henry F., 1973-1974
      - "W" miscellaneous, 1984-1990, undated
    - Judicial Conferences (Box 80)
      - Second Circuit
        - 1962, Manchester, Vt., 1961-1962
        - 1963, Whiteface, N.Y., 1962-1963
        - 1964, Manchester, Vt., 1963-1964
        - 1965, New York, N.Y.
          - Correspondence, 1964-1965
          - Miscellany, 1964-1965, undated
        - 1966, Whiteface, N.Y.
          - Correspondence, 1966
          - Judicial disability, circa 1966
          - Miscellany, 1966
        - 1967, Manchester, Vt., 1967
        - 1968, Whiteface, N.Y., 1967-1968
        - 1969, Manchester, Vt., 1968-1969
        - 1970, Lake Placid, N.Y., 1969-1970
        - 1971, Manchester, Vt. (Box 81)
          - Correspondence, 1970-1972, (2 folders)
          - Introduction of newly-appointed and retiring judges, 1971
          - Miscellany, 1971, undated
        - 1972, Whiteface, N.Y.
          - Correspondence, 1971-1972
          - Executive session, 1972
          - Miscellany, 1972, undated
          - Planning and Program Committee, 1971-1972
        - 1973, Buck Hill Falls, Pa.
          - Correspondence, 1972-1973, (2 folders)
          - Executive session, 1973
          - Jury program, 1972-1973 (Box 82)
          - Miscellany, 1972-1973, undated
        - 1974, Buck Hill Falls, Pa.
          - Correspondence, 1974-1975
          - Miscellany, 1974
          - Planning and Program Committee, 1973-1974, (3 folders)
          - Sentencing, 1974
        - 1975, Buck Hill Falls, Pa.
          - Correspondence, 1974-1975
          - Invitees (Box 83)
            - Correspondence, 1974-1975, undated
            - Lists, circa 1974-1975
          - Miscellany, 1975
          - News clippings, 1975
        - 1975, Buck Hill Falls, Pa.
          - Panel discussions
            - Correspondence, 1974-1975
            - Miscellany, 1975, undated
          - Planning and Program Committee, 1974-1975, undated
          - Southern District of New York, resolution, 1975
        - 1976, Buck Hill Falls, Pa.
          - Change of date survey, 1975
          - Correspondence, 1975-1976, (3 folders) (Box 84)
          - Miscellany, 1975-1976, undated
          - News clippings, 1976
          - Panel discussions, 1976, (4 folders)
          - Speeches, 1976
        - 1977, Buck Hill Falls, Pa. (Box 85)
          - Change of date/location survey, 1976
          - Correspondence, 1976-1977
          - Miscellany, 1977, undated
          - Notebook, 1977
          - Planning and Program Committee, 1976-1977
          - Speeches, 1977
        - 1978, Buck Hill Falls, Pa.
          - Correspondence, 1977-1978
          - Miscellany, 1978, undated
          - Panel discussions, 1978
          - Planning and Program Committee, 1978 (Box 86)
          - Program material, 1978
          - Speeches, 1978
        - 1979, Buck Hill Falls, Pa.
          - Correspondence, 1978-1979, (2 folders)
          - Miscellany, 1979, undated
          - News clippings, 1979
          - Photographs, 1979
          - Planning and Program Committee, 1978-1979, undated
          - Program material, 1979
          - Speeches, 1979
        - 1980, Buck Hill Falls, Pa.
          - Correspondence, 1979-1980, (2 folders)
          - Executive session, 1980
          - Miscellany, 1979-1980
          - Program planning, 1979-1980 (Box 87)
          - Speeches, 1980
        - 1981, Buck Hill Falls, Pa.
          - Correspondence, 1980-1981
          - Miscellany, 1981, undated
          - Speeches, 1981
        - 1982, Hershey, Pa.
          - Correspondence, 1981-1982
          - Jury committee, 1968-1982, undated
          - Miscellany, 1982
        - 1983, Hershey, Pa., 1983
        - 1984, Hartford, Conn.
          - Correspondence, 1984
          - Miscellany, 1984, undated
          - Notebooks, 1984
        - 1985, Hershey, Pa., 1984-1985 (Box 88)
        - 1986, Bolton Landing, N.Y.
          - Articles, 1977, 1985-1986, undated
          - Miscellany, 1986, undated
          - Notebook, 1986
        - 1987, Hershey, Pa., 1987
        - 1989, Bolton Landing, N.Y., 1984-1990
        - 1990, Bolton Landing, N.Y., 1990
        - 1991, Rye Brook, N.Y., 1991
      - Tenth Circuit, Moran, Wyo., 1963
      - United States, Washington D.C.
        - Mar. 1967, 1966-1967
        - Sept. 1967, 1967
        - Feb. 1968, 1967-1968
        - Sept. 1968, 1968
        - Mar. 1969, 1968-1969 (Box 89)
        - Oct.-Nov. 1969, 1969
        - Mar. 1970, 1969-1970
        - Oct. 1970, 1970
        - Mar. 1971, 1970-1971
        - Apr. 1972, 1971-1972
        - Oct. 1972, 1972-1973
        - Miscellaneous, 1971-1991
    - Judicial Council of the Second Circuit, 1978-1982
    - Judicial tenure, 1978
    - Juror utilization workshop, New York, N.Y., 1971-1972, undated
    - Justice Department
      - Attorney General's Advocacy Institute, 1976-1981
      - Correspondence, 1962-1963, 1974-1982
      - Evaluations of judicial nominees by New York City Bar Association, 1991
      - Meador, Daniel J.
        - Correspondence, 1977-1978, undated
        - Miscellany, 1977-1978, undated
    - Juvenile Justice Standards Project (Box 90)
      - Correspondence
        - May 1972-Apr. 1976, (7 folders)
        - May 1976-May 1982, undated, (8 folders) (Box 91)
      - Meetings (Box 92)
        - General, 1970-1980, undated, (8 folders)
        - Notebooks (Box 93)
          - Oct. 1971, (2 folders)
          - Jan. 1974, (2 folders)
          - Dec. 1974, (4 folders)
          - Dec. 1974, (2 folders) (Box 94)
          - May 1975, (3 folders)
          - Oct. 1975, (3 folders)
          - Jan. 1976, (7 folders) (Box 95)
          - Jan. 1976, (7 folders) (Box 96)
          - May 1976, (7 folders) (Box 97)
          - May 1976, (2 folders) (Box 98)
          - Nov. 1977, (4 folders)
          - Oct. 1978
          - Nov. 1979
          - Undated, (3 folders)
        - Transcript, 1974 (Box 99)
      - Miscellany, 1972-1980, undated, (2 folders)
      - News clippings, 1973-1982, undated, (2 folders)
      - Reports
        - 1971-1972, (3 folders)
        - 1972-1974, (6 folders) (Box 100)
        - 1973-1976, (7 folders) (Box 101)
        - 1976-1978, undated, (8 folders) (Box 102)
        - Undated, (2 folders) (Box 103)
      - Speeches and writings, 1974-1982, undated, (4 folders)
    - Krasowski, Roberta, 1982 (Box 104)
    - Law clerks
      - Draft deferment, 1963
      - Memoranda, 1966-1974, undated
      - Placement, 1982-1983
    - Mergers and acquisitions notebook, 1972[?], (3 folders)
    - Merit awards ceremony, 1976-1978, undated
    - Miscellany, 1978, 1989-1991, undated
    - Multidistrict litigation, 1968
    - National Center for State Courts, 1971
    - National Conference of Bar Presidents, 1975
    - National Conference of Judicial Councils, 1971-1980
    - National Conference on the Judiciary, 1970-1971
    - National Lawyers Club, 1966-1981
    - New York County Lawyers' Association (Box 105)
      - Correspondence, 1961-1989, (2 folders)
      - Miscellany, 1970-1977, undated
    - New York Criminal and Civil Courts Bar Association, 1974-1975
    - New York Patent Law Association, 1965-1983
    - New York State associations, miscellaneous, 1966, 1976, 1988-1989
    - New York State Bar Association, 1962-1988
    - Newsletter for the second circuit, 1975-1991, (2 folders)
    - Ninth Circuit resolutions, 1972 (Box 106)
    - President's Commission on Organized Crime, 1983-1986, undated
    - President's Commission on Selection of Judges for the Second Circuit, 1978-1980, undated
    - President's Reorganization Project, 1977
    - Press releases, 1976-1979
    - Prisoners
      - Correspondence, 1966-1977
      - State Prisoner Civil Rights Action Committee, 1972-1973
    - Prisons, 1974-1975
    - Quote notebook, circa 1970, (3 folders)
    - Roscoe Pound Conference, St. Paul, Minn., notebook, 1976, (2 folders)
    - Rules, 1968-1990, (8 folders) (Box 107)
    - Security, 1971-1980, (3 folders) (Box 108)
    - Seminars for
      - Circuit court judges, 1972-1973, undated
      - Newly-appointed judges
        - Feb. 1962, Monterey, Calif., 1962
        - Apr.-May 1962, Norfolk, Va., 1962, (3 folders)
        - Aug. 1962, Dearborn, Mich.
          - Miscellany, 1962
          - Notebooks, 1962, (5 folders) (Box 109)
        - July 1963, postponed, 1963
        - Feb. 1964, Denver, Colo.
          - Correspondence, 1963-1965
          - Miscellany, 1964, undated
          - Notebook, 1964, (2 folders)
        - June-July 1965, Denver, Colo. (Box 110)
          - Correspondence, 1964-1967, (4 folders)
          - Miscellany, 1965, undated
        - May-June 1968, Denver, Colo.
          - Correspondence, 1968
          - Miscellany, 1968, undated
        - July 1968, Berkeley, Calif.
          - Miscellany, 1968
          - Notebook, 1968
        - Oct.-Nov. 1968, Washington, D.C.
          - Miscellany, 1968
          - Notebook, 1968, (2 folders) (Box 111)
        - Apr.-May 1973, Washington, D.C., 1973
        - Miscellany, 1966-1972, undated
        - Planning committee, 1964-1971, (3 folders)
    - Sentencing
      - Guidelines, 1976-1987, undated
      - Institutes, 1960-1966, 1973, 1981
      - Miscellany, 1962-1967, 1983, undated
      - Reports (Box 112)
        - Miscellaneous, 1982-1983, undated
        - Second circuit study, 1974
    - Soviet Union's Justice Minister Yakolev, 1990
    - Spanish-speaking clients of the court, 1977, undated
    - Speedy Trial Act
      - Committee meetings, 1975-1978, undated
      - Correspondence, 1974-1983
      - Districts
        - Connecticut, 1976
        - Eastern New York, 1975-1981
        - Northern New York, 1976[?]
        - Southern New York, 1978 (Box 113)
        - Vermont, 1976
        - Western New York, 1976[?]
      - Guidelines, 1978-1979, undated
      - Miscellany, 1977-1979, undated
    - Standing directions to the clerk for the hearing and disposition of motions, 1954-1971, undated
    - State of the circuit, 1975-1977
    - State-federal judicial councils, 1981
    - Statistics
      - 1961-1969, (5 folders)
      - 1970-1981, (13 folders) (Box 114)
      - 1982-1991, (2 folders) (Box 115)
    - Student practice in the courts
      - Correspondence, 1973-1977, (2 folders)
      - Eastern district of New York, 1975, undated
      - McKay, Robert B., 1973-1975, undated
      - Rules, 1975, undated
    - Three-judge courts, 1973-1975
    - United States commissioner system, 1965-1966, (2 folders)
- Subject File, 1945-1992 (Box 116-130)
  Correspondence, news clippings, reports, press releases, and miscellaneous material.
  Arranged alphabetically by name of correspondent, organization, or subject.
  - Abortion, 1964-1974, undated (Box 116)
  - Abrams, Floyd, 1975-1990, undated
  - Address and telephone lists, undated
  - Advocacy, 1966, 1973-1976
  - Agate, Anita K., 1974-1991, undated
  - American Civil Liberties Union, 1965, 1975, 1990
  - American Lawyer, 1982-1986
  - Anecdotes, 1990-1991, undated
  - Annenberg, Walter H., 1977, 1989-1991, undated
  - Anniversaries of service on the federal bench
    - 20th, 1969
    - 25th, 1974
    - 30th, 1979
    - 40th
      - Correspondence, 1989-1992, undated
      - Miscellany, 1989-1990, undated (Box 117)
  - Anti-Defamation League of B'nai B'rith, 1960-1991, undated, (4 folders)
  - Armour, Frances, 1970-1977
  - Armstrong, Edward C., 1968-1969
  - Aspen Institute for Humanistic Studies, Aspen, Colo., 1970-1991
  - "A" miscellaneous, 1967-1991, undated
  - Baer, Rudolf, 1976-1986
  - Balanced Budget and Emergency Deficit Control Act of 1985, 1986
  - Bartels, John R., 1967, 1979-1989
  - Bauman, Arnold, 1965-1967
  - Bell, J. Raymond, 1967-1976
  - Benjamin N. Cardozo School of Law, Yeshiva University, New York, N.Y., 1980-1987
  - Biographical material, 1953-1990, undated, (2 folders) (Box 118)
  - Blough, Roger M., 1968-1985
  - Blumenfeld, M. Joseph, 1969-1975
  - Bodin, Harry Sabbath, 1976-1978
  - Borinstein, Joan, 1962-1991
  - Brandstetter, Frank M., 1971-1978
  - Brill, Arthur P., 1985-1988
  - Broderick, Vincent L., 1976-1979
  - Brookings Institution, Washington, D.C., 1964-1981, undated
  - Brooklyn Law Review, 1970-1988
  - Buck Hill Inn, Buck Hill Falls, Pa., 1978-1986
  - Burchill, William R., 1990-1991 (Box 119)
  - Bush, George, 1986-1989
  - "B" miscellaneous, 1964-1989
  - Cameras in the courtroom, 1973-1991, undated, (2 folders)
  - Cannon, Mark W., 1976-1988
  - Celler, Emanuel, 1973, undated
  - Cherne, Leo, 1972, 1983-1990
  - Clare, Robert L., 1973-1980
  - Columbia University, New York, N.Y., 1951-1987
  - Council on Legal Education for Professional Responsibility
    - New York, N.Y., 1973-1976
  - Cromwell, James H. R., 1976-1980
  - Crowley, Joseph R., 1985-1986, undated
  - Cullman, Edgar M., 1979-1988
  - "C" miscellaneous, 1960-1962, 1970-1990
  - Daily News, 1974-1986, undated
  - Davis, Samuel, 1980-1987
  - DeWitt Clinton High School, New York, N.Y., 1976, undated
  - Dickinson University School of Law, Carlisle, Pa., 1977-1991 (Box 120)
  - Diplock, Kenneth, 1977-1983, undated
  - Disposition of court records, 1982
  - Dodd, Christopher J., 1974-1989
  - Dolan, Anthony, 1982-1991
  - Drug abuse, 1957-1962, 1986-1989, undated, (2 folders)
  - "D" miscellaneous, 1961-1991, undated
  - Early, Bert H., 1981
  - Ebersole, Joseph L., 1970-1972, 1982
  - Editor & Publisher, 1977, 1986
  - Eulogies, 1962-1966, 1977, 1984-1989
  - Fair trial-free press (Box 121)
    - Conference
      - Agenda and minutes, 1970-1979
      - Correspondence, 1970-1979, (2 folders)
      - General, 1973-1980, undated, (3 folders)
    - Miscellany, 1968-1991, undated
  - Feinberg, Abraham, 1965-1989
  - Feinberg, Kenneth R., 1979-1981
  - Filartiga v. Pena-Irala, 1991, undated
  - First amendment, 1967-1986, undated
  - Fiske, Robert B., 1976-1978
  - Foley, William E., 1964-1990 (Box 122)
  - Fordham University Law School, New York, N.Y.
    - Correspondence, 1974-1992, (2 folders)
    - Honorary degree, 1972-1973
    - Miscellany, 1972-1988
    - Moot court competition, 1975-1979, 1991, undated
    - Portrait unveiling, 1989-1990, undated
  - Forster, Arnold, 1979-1991
  - Freedman, Eric M., 1986-1991
  - Fresh Air Fund, 1988-1991
  - Friedersdorp, Max L., 1982
  - Friedman, Max, 1985-1986
  - Friendly, Fred W., 1983-1986
  - "F" miscellaneous, 1969, 1981-1988
  - Gates, Samuel E. and Philomene A., 1978-1990 (Box 123)
  - Ginsberg, Henry and Mildred, 1966-1979
  - Glasser, Stephen A., 1977-1982
  - Golden, William T., 1980-1989
  - Golding, Samuel, 1964-1967
  - Goldstein, Tom, 1979-1985
  - Gossett, William T., 1971, 1978-1985, undated
  - Gould, Milton S., 1968, 1979-1989
  - Green, Bill, 1978-1989
  - Griswold, Erwin N., 1965-1971, 1979-1985
  - "G" miscellaneous, 1967-1986, undated
  - Haft, Robert J., 1969-1991
  - Handler, Milton, 1971-1991, undated
  - Harvard University Law School, Cambridge, Mass.
    - Miscellany, 1977, 1990-1991
    - Moot court competition, 1975, undated
    - Kaufman fellowships
      - Correspondence, 1989-1991, undated, (2 folders)
      - Inaugural dinner, 1989-1990, undated, (2 folders) (Box 124)
      - Miscellany, 1990-1991, undated
      - News clippings, 1989-1992, undated
      - Press releases, 1989-1990
  - Hazard, Geoffrey C., 1967-1972
  - Heflin, Howell, 1980-1991
  - Herlands, Gertrude C., 1966-1969, 1981
  - Heymann, Philip B., 1981-1982
  - Horan, Francis H., 1962-1979
  - Humphrey, Hubert H., 1965-1968, 1962-1979
  - "H" miscellaneous, 1972-1987
  - Illness, correspondence during, 1987
  - Inaugural committee for President-elect Johnson, 1964-1965, undated
  - International Terrorism Symposium, London, England, 1983, undated
  - Javits, Jacob K., 1957-1981, undated (Box 125)
  - Jones, John Haydn, 1975-1987
  - Judicature, 1975-1981
  - Judicial compensation, 1960-1963, 1983-1985, (2 folders)
  - Judicial reform, 1961-1963
  - Jury reform, 1972-1974, undated
  - "J" miscellaneous, 1968-1989
  - Klein, Fannie J., 1968-1982, undated
  - Kostelanetz, Boris, 1972-1988
  - "K" miscellaneous, 1983-1990
  - Legal Aid Society
    - Correspondence, 1963-1988, (2 folders)
    - Miscellany, 1949, 1972-1979
  - Lowe, Florence, 1965-1975
  - "L" miscellaneous, 1974-1990, undated
  - Marden, Orison Swett, 1970-1979 (Box 126)
  - Mays, Herbert R., 1966-1987
  - Mazur, Paul, 1969-1973
  - Mecham, L. Ralph, 1986-1991
  - Medal of Freedom
    - Correspondence, 1987-1989, (2 folders)
    - Miscellany, 1987-1988, undated
  - Meserve, Robert W., 1972-1989
  - Mount Sinai Medical Center, New York, N.Y., 1975-1991
  - "M" miscellaneous, 1951-1988, undated
  - Naturalization, 1950-1958, undated
  - Nevins, Theodore, circa 1953
  - New York Law School, New York, N.Y., 1968, 1976-1991 (Box 127)
  - New York Post, 1968-1972
  - New York Times
    - Correspondence, 1971-1991
    - First amendment seminar, 1976
  - New York University, New York, N.Y., 1958-1989, (2 folders)
  - Newhouse, Donald E. and Susan, 1980-1991
  - Newhouse, Samuel I., Jr., 1982-1990
  - Newhouse, Samuel I., Sr., and Mitzi, 1963-1980
  - News clippings, 1947-1991, undated, (3 folders)
  - Noonan, Kaufman and Eagan, 1945-1951 (Box 128)
  - "N" miscellaneous, 1974-1991
  - O'Connor, John, Cardinal, 1985-1987
  - Olney, Warren, 1967-1968
  - Phi Alpha Delta Law Fraternity, 1964-1965, 1975
  - Photographic portraits, undated
  - Pomona College, Claremont, Calif., 1968-1974, 1982
  - Practicing Law Institute, New York, N.Y., 1965-1976
  - Press releases, 1976, undated
  - Putterman, David J., 1965, 1976
  - "P" miscellaneous, 1988, undated
  - Reagan, Ronald, 1980-1991
  - Regan, Donald T., 1985-1986
  - Rifkind, Simon H., 1968-1991, undated, (3 folders)
  - Rosenberg, Irwin H., Doris and Gerald A., 1949-1990, undated, (2 folders)
  - Rosenberg, Maurice, 1970-1979 (Box 129)
  - Rosentiel, Lewis S., 1967-1979
  - Rusk, Howard A., 1968-1981
  - "R" miscellaneous, 1967-1983
  - St. Louis Globe-Democrat, 1970-1974, 1983
  - Saloman, Sidney and Jeannette, 1947-1975, 1989
  - Sann, Paul, 1975-1977, undated
  - Sarnoff, Robert W., 1968-1974, 1981, undated
  - Schwartz, Arthur H., 1968-1971
  - Shafroth, Morrison, 1960-1965
  - Shafroth, Will, 1960-1967
  - Shapiro, David L., 1968-1970
  - Simon, William G., 1966-1988
  - State University of New York, Buffalo, New York, 1975-1979
  - "S" miscellaneous, 1957-1958, 1975-1985
  - Taylor, Henry J., 1974-1977
  - Thau, Benjamin, 1955-1972
  - Thode, E. Wayne, 1969-1972, undated
  - Time, Inc., 1969-1980
  - "T" miscellaneous, 1972-1977, 1990
  - United States v. Rosenberg
    - Correspondence, 1958, 1974-1990, undated
    - Documents obtained through the Freedom of Information Act, 1951-1976 (Box 130)
    - Miscellany, 1974-1976, undated
    - New Meaning of Treason, 1964
    - News clippings, 1953-1986, undated
  - University of Virginia, Charlottesville, Va., 1974-1980, undated
  - "U" miscellaneous, 1970, 1978
  - Vacation, 1982
  - Wall Street Journal, 1975-1985, undated
  - White House, 1968-1989
  - Widgery, John, 1974-1990, undated
  - Wilders, James C., 1967-1974
  - "W" miscellaneous, 1967, 1981-1989
  - Zelenko, Herbert, 1961-1962
- Speeches and Writings, 1945-1991 (Box 131-143)
  Articles, book reviews, letters to the editor, research material, and speeches.
  Organized alphabetically by type of writing and arranged chronologically therein.
  - Index (incomplete), undated, (3 folders) (Box 131)
  - Articles
    - 1951, Feb., "Observations on Transfers under Section 1404(a) of the New Judicial Code"